Chapter 1: Befuddled by Love

Energy is the essence of all life.

Energy arts are the means by which to cultivate the essence of life.

Reaching the peak of cultivation brings a host of fantastic and amazing abilities.

Energy arts experts could break walls with their hands, hear sounds as quiet as the footsteps of an ant, walk on water, breathe fire, become impervious to all sorts of weapons, fuse their energy with the clouds, sustain themselves by absorbing energy instead of eating food, and even track enemies by locking down onto their souls….

Rich-Lush Continent. Yanhaven. [1]

It was a populous and affluent place; despite it being nighttime, streams of horses and carriages could be seen on the streets, and the city was bathed with bright lamplight.

It was midsummer, and dark clouds filled the night sky. The muffled rumble of thunder could be heard in the distance, and from the dense humidity in the air, it seemed rain would begin to fall soon.

In a relatively remote corner of the city, the ground suddenly shuddered, and then a hole exploded into being.

A young man leaped out of the hole, as agile as a cat. He appeared to be about seventeen or eighteen years of age, was dressed head to toe in black clothing, and was carrying an exquisitely crafted box.

This young man was Yang Qi who, like many others, cultivated energy arts. [2] [3]

He was a young master from the Yang Clan, an aristocratic clan from Yanhaven. He was also relatively famous within the city as a powerful master of energy arts. He wasn't very old, and wasn’t necessarily tall and well-built. But from his every move and action, it was obvious the mysterious energy flowing through him was ready to erupt out at any moment.

As he stood there at the edge of the hole, he circulated his energy, and intense rumbling sounds could be heard, shocking to the extreme.

“I guess it won’t be long before I reach the fifth phase of energy arts, the Energy Eruption level. Then I’ll be able to cast my true energy outside of my body. That will make me a real expert! My progress will be incredible!” [4]

He glanced back at the towering city wall, looking very pleased at having circumvented it the way he did. Then he blurred into motion, disappearing like a black panther into the dark forest surrounding the city.

Yang Qi had long since cultivated his energy arts to the fourth phase, the Energy Refinement level.

On the Rich-Lush Continent, experts who cultivated energy arts divided them into nine phases.

First was Energy Growth, in which one built up energy in the body.

Second was Energy Circulation, in which one sent vital energy flowing through one’s meridian channels.

Third was Energy Convergence, when the vital energy was gathered in a central location, the sea of energy.

Fourth was Energy Refinement, in which the gathered vital energy was refined and purified.

Fifth was Energy Eruption. In that phase, one could use energy arts externally to harm enemies.

The first four phases —Absorption, Circulation, Convergence, and Refinement— were all internal, and although they could be used to strengthen one's body, did little else. Upon reaching the fifth phase, Energy Eruption, one’s body was completely transformed, making it possible to unleash energy arts in combat.

Only upon reaching the Energy Eruption level, could one be considered to be a truly powerful expert.

Thus, the fifth phase was considered a major watershed point in the cultivation of energy arts.

In that level, it was possible to unleash the Hundred Paces Divine Fist, a technique that could inflict damage a hundred paces away, even to the point of shattering trees. Such battle prowess was so extraordinary that one person who wielded it could defeat a hundred who could not.

The sixth phase was called the Energy Weapon level, in which one could use energy to form corporeal weapons.

The seventh level was the Energy Manifestation level. In that phase, energy arts could be used to summon ferocious beasts, or wings that could send one flying through the sky.

The eighth phase, Energy Incarnation, led to an ability called Mind Incarnation, in which the practitioner could create a defensive energy barrier of nearly impenetrable strength.

The ninth phase was called the Master of Energy level. Unfortunately, Yang Qi was very unlikely to ever become such a grandmaster of energy arts.

According to the rumors, experts in the Master of Energy level could eventually seize life from the heavens, and thus reach the Lifeseizing level. Lifeseizers essentially experienced a rebirth, and would acquire a lifespan multiple times longer than ordinary energy arts practitioners. Yang Qi had never even seen a person like that.

**

After running through the forest for a short time, Yang Qi caught sight of a young woman in an azure garment, standing there proudly, her back to him.

“Lan’er!” he called out. “I got the Latent Dragon Pill! It wasn’t easy, but thanks to my connections in the city, I managed to get into the city magistrate’s mansion, break into his treasure-house, and steal the pill!”

Looking excitedly at the young woman, he held out the crafted box he had been carrying this entire time.

The young woman turned, revealing a spectacularly beautiful face.

“So, Yang Qi, you finally succeeded.” Reaching out with fingers as beautiful as ivory, she said, “Hand it over so I can take a look.”

“Alright.” Without the slightest hesitation, Yang Qi handed the box to the young woman.

She took it, then opened it to reveal a fiery-red medicinal pill. A medicinal aroma immediately filled the area, and the pill itself seemed to flicker as if with flames, casting red light onto the young woman’s face, making her look even more attractive than before.

“Okay, Lan’er,” Yang Qi said. “I got you the Latent Dragon Pill. Now we can run off together like you promised, right? Come on, let’s get going.”

“I'm sorry, Yang Qi,” she said, tucking the box away into her garment. Looking at him coldly, she continued, “I have an important matter to attend to, so I won’t be running off with you. In fact, don't ever bring up the subject again.”

Her words struck him like a lightning bolt falling from blue skies.

Staggering backward a few paces, his face draining of blood, he said, “Lan’er, I put myself in great danger for you! I stole a Latent Dragon Pill from the city magistrate’s mansion, all because you said we would run off together. Now you’re changing your mind? Why? Why would you do something like this?”

Suddenly, a voice sounded out, “How about I explain?" A moment later, a figure emerged from the darkness of the forest. He was a handsome young man, tall and strapping, clad in a suit of armor. From the way he looked down his nose at Yang Qi, it was obvious how much of an arrogant and haughty person he was.

“Do you really think that Lan’er, a stunning princess of Yundale-by-the-Sea, would care about a little punk from the Yang Clan? Your clan might be important in Yanhaven, but let me tell you this: Not even the princes of Yanhaven would think of trying to pursue Lan’er. She used you! Understand, you naive fool? You know the saying about the ugly toad lusting after the swan? That's you!” [5]

“Is all this true, Lan’er?” Yang Qi asked, his face ashen, but still holding onto whatever faint scraps of hope still existed in his heart.

However, the next thing Lan’er said crushed that hope out of existence.

Face incomparably cold, she said, “It's true, Yang Qi. I used you to get the Latent Dragon Pill. That having been said, I don't want to hurt you, so why don’t you just leave.”

“You….” Yang Qi was trembling, and his hands and feet were already as cold as ice. “How could you be like this, Lan’er? Go? Where am I supposed to go to? I stole a Latent Dragon Pill! I can’t go back home, and the guards from Yanhaven are probably already chasing after me. How about you at least give the Latent Dragon Pill back to me, and we call it even?”

The young man in the armor laughed coldly. “Give it back to you? Quit dreaming, punk. Who in their right mind would spit their meat out after taking a bite? Beat it. If you even think about stirring up trouble, I’ll make you regret it….”

“You….” Without any warning, Yang Qi suddenly exploded into action. As powerful as a tiger, and as lithe as a snake, he lunged at the armored young man, his hands swinging through the air with axe-like viciousness.

“Corpse-Chomping White Tiger!” he shouted, immediately resorting to a deadly energy art move unique to the Yang Clan. At its highest level, this energy art could be used to summon an enormous white tiger, fiendish to the extreme and strong enough to reduce any enemy to nothing more than a corpse. Of course, Yang Qi was far from being able to use it in that way.

“Looking to die?” the armored young man said, his eyes flickering with scorn.

Whoosh!

A transparent wave of energy shot out from his hand, slamming into Yang Qi. Before he could even fully execute his Corpse-Chomping White Tiger, he was slammed into the ground, where he vomited up a mouthful of blood.

Eyes shining with shock, he looked up and said, “You’re in the fifth phase of energy arts, the Energy Eruption level….”

“That’s right,” the armored young man replied. “To me, you’re like nothing more than an ant. “Corpse-Chomping White Tiger is a deadly move, but when you use it, you look like a kid play-fighting with his friends.”

Yang Qi struggled to his feet. Eyes flickering with hatred, he said, “Who are you…?”

“I'm Song Haishan, Lan’er’s older cousin. Only a few days ago, she was accepted to be an advanced disciple in the number one organization in Rich-Lush Continent, the Demi-Immortal Institute. Do you know how important that makes her? You really think you have any hope of getting close to her? Wait… did you ask who I was because you think you’re going to come after me for revenge? Hm. As the saying goes, if you cut the grass but not the root, it will grow again when the spring breeze blows. I guess letting you go free isn't really an option.” [6]

Even as the words were leaving his mouth, Song Haishan’s energy began to build up inside of him.

“So,” Yang Qi growled, “you’re the one they call the best of the best in Yundale-by-the-Sea. Well, I'm still going to kill you. And as for you, Yun Hailan, you lied to me, and I swear that one day, I'm going to pay you back for that.” [7]

“Seems leaving you alive is definitely the wrong thing to do….” Song Haishan growled, preparing to take action.

“Enough, cousin,” Yun Hailan said, reaching out to block his path. Then she looked in the direction of Yanhaven. “The guards are already on their way. There’s no reason to kill him. Come on, let’s go….” With that, she vanished into the night, leaving behind a single sentence. “After I'm a disciple at the Demi-Immortal Institute, Yang Qi, I’ll make this up to you.”

Song Haishan looked at Yang Qi with a sneer. “Hmph. Looks like you get to live a bit longer, punk. Lan’er doesn’t want you dead because she doesn’t want your blood on her hands. Fine. But the city magistrate of Yanhaven isn’t going to let you off the hook. So you won’t be alive for much longer regardless.”

Chuckling in sinister fashion, he turned to follow Yun Hailan.

“Yun Hailan….” Yang Qi murmured. Spitting out some blood, he looked in the direction into which she and Song Haishan had just vanished, fully aware that they were far superior to him in terms of energy arts.

Suddenly, he thought back to everything that had led up to this point. In the course of helping with the clan business, he had encountered Yun Hailan, whom he had fallen for at first sight. She treated him with tenderness and compassion for a time, whereupon she asked for his help to get the Latent Dragon Pill. He had pondered the matter for some time before making his decision. And now, here he was.

As he stood there, he circulated his energy arts and tried to decide what to do. He knew that the city guards of Yanhaven were coming for him. He had brought humiliation to his clan, and would surely be severely punished if he were caught.

As he was trying to recover, he suddenly heard voices. And then, only a moment later, several figures appeared in front of him.

One of them was a man wearing a suit of cold-forged iron armor that weighed no less than a hundred pounds, making him look like a vicious beast. As soon as Yang Qi saw that armored man, his heart sank into despair.

He was Luo Hun, one of the special guards from the city magistrate’s mansion, a brutal and fierce man whose cultivation had long since surpassed the Energy Eruption level. [8]

“Hand over the Latent Dragon Pill you stole, Yang Qi. If you do, I’ll spare your life….”

Luo Hun’s eyes glittered like an animal’s, not a human’s, and his cold-forged iron armor radiated a powerful killing aura. Not waiting for a response, he stepped forward and struck Yang Qi’s dantian region with a palm strike, aiming directly at his sea of energy.

Yet again, blood sprayed out of Yang Qi’s mouth as the energy arts he had cultivated from the age of five to eighteen were crippled.

“You… crippled my energy arts…?” A look of complete despair overtook his face. With the sea of energy in his dantian region destroyed, it would be impossible for him to converge energy. Henceforth, he would be doomed to be nothing more than an ordinary person.

“You had the audacity to steal a Latent Dragon Pill,” Luo Hun said coldly. “Crippling your energy arts is actually letting you off a bit lightly. Because you’re a young master of the Yang Clan, and also for the sake of your aunt, I won’t put you to death immediately. Men, tie him up against that tree. I'm going back to the city to report to the magistrate and get new orders. Stay here and preserve the scene of the crime. I’ll have some people from the Yang Clan come out to take a look at the situation.”

“Yes sir,” replied the other special guards. Without any hesitation, they tied Yang Qi up against a nearby tree, and then began to patrol the area.

As for Luo Hun, it didn't matter that he was wearing a suit of cold-forged iron armor that weighed over a hundred pounds. He sped into motion like a bird taking flight, heading directly back toward Yanhaven.

Around then, numerous bolts of lightning began to crackle in the dark sky above. The rain that had been brewing all this time seemed to have reached a boiling point, and began to fall, joined by the lightning, which looked like silver snakes lashing at the ground.

“This rain is really heavy,” said one of the guards, looking up nervously. “And what’s with all the lightning?”

Suddenly, a bolt of lightning smashed into a distant tree, causing it to burst into flame despite the heavy rain. The sight of so much lightning falling within the rain was truly a frightening sight.

Looking completely frightened, another guard said, “This lightning really seems strange. I’ve never seen anything like it. I've heard that not even people in the Master of Energy level can survive being struck by heavenly lightning like this. If we stay in this forest, we’re going to get killed! Let’s get out of here!”

“What about this little punk?”

“Don’t worry, his martial arts have been crippled. Besides, he's all tied up. How could he possibly escape? Flying?”

Shivering in fear, the guards turned and fled.

However, even as they made their way out of the trees, a brilliantly shining bolt of lightning fell into the forest and smashed into the tree upon which Yang Qi had been bound.

Instantly, Yang Qi’s entire body filled with glittering electricity. Then, the smell of burning flesh filled the air.

1. Yanhaven/Rich-Lush: The Yan means “swallow (bird)”. As will be revealed shortly, there is also a clan of the same name, which is why I’m not translating this character in the name of the city. When it comes to the cities in this novel, I am doing something a bit different from my other translations. Instead of simply translating them as something like Yan City, I’m going to use some common suffixes for most cities, such as -haven, -forth, -ville, etc. The reason for this is that using the word “city” in the actual name of city is not very common in English. Although there is a New York City in America, most other cities have a single proper noun as their name. That’s the standard I’m aiming for in this story. In terms of "Rich-Lush" I understand that it sounds a bit odd, but there is a reason I'm translating it that way.

2. Yang Qi: Yang is a common surname which also means “poplar tree”. Qi means “extraordinary, astonishing, wonderful, rare, surprising, etc.” It's pronounced "yawng chee".

3. “Energy arts” is both the name of a broad cultivation level, and also the term to describe the “arts” practice within that overarching level. For all intents and purposes, “energy arts” is synonymous with “martial arts”, although both terms do get used.

4. There is a reason why this type of energy is called 'true' energy, although the explanation won't come for many, many chapters.

5. Yundale-by-the-Sea: Yun means cloud.

6. Song Haishan: Song is a common surname. Hai means “sea” and Shan means “mountain”.

7. Yun Hailan: Yun means “cloud” and Hai means “sea”. Lan means “mountain mist, mountain haze, vapour, etc.”

8. Luo Hun: Luo is a really complicated character that can mean a lot of things. In addition to being a surname, it can mean “sieve, silk gauze, to collect, to spread out, to catch, to gather, to sift. It is also found in a lot of transliterated religious terms. It is also part of the term “Allheaven” from my previous translations. Hun means soul, specifically the “spiritual soul”.

Chapter 2: Profiting from a Disaster

Yang Qi couldn’t have been more demoralized.

With a single palm strike, Luo Hun crippled his sea of energy, destroying his energy arts and ensuring that his cultivation base had no hope of ever progressing.

And who could ever have guessed that he would then have the misfortune of being struck by lightning?

As the mighty lightning bolt slammed into the tree, and then him, his eyes felt like they were going to explode, forcing him to close them.

‘Am I going to die?’ he thought. ‘Well, I guess that would be good. Then I wouldn’t have to endure being a laughingstock the rest of my life.’

As the lightning entered his body, he felt unprecedented pain and heat, as though millions upon millions of blades were slicing into his flesh and bones.

However, he didn’t die. The power of the lightning ripped through his muscles, his skeleton, and his meridians, eventually causing a vortex to spring up in his dantian region.

As a result, his destroyed sea of energy suddenly underwent strange and bizarre transformations. The spiraling electricity began to assume a shape, until it looked like a violent, berserk mammoth, almost dragon-like in its ferocity.

If anyone had been able to witness what was happening inside of him, they would have seen what looked like an enormous mammoth made of lightning, trumpeting like mad.

The lightning did not dissipate; it coursed down through the tree into Yang Qi, causing the tree to burst into flame.

Eventually, Yang Qi saw a tiny golden person in the lightning, who flew directly into his forehead. After that, his mind felt like it was bulging on the verge of exploding, whereupon he passed out.

The guards, who were out of the forest by this time, were all visibly taken aback. They were close enough to have clearly seen the lightning striking the tree and catching it on fire. And they could even see Yang Qi slumped down into the mud, seemingly dead.

“What do we do now?” said one of the guards.

“Him getting struck by lightning doesn’t have anything to do with us,” said another.

“You go back to the city to report the matter to the exalted Luo Hun. The kid committed an unforgivable crime, but he does come from a rich and powerful clan, after all. If he dies like this and the matter isn't handled properly, it could cause big problems in Yanhaven.”

One of the other guards immediately turned to run back to the city.

However, before he could take more than a few steps, he saw a hulking figure up ahead, clad in metal armor.

Breaking out in a cold sweat, the guard flopped down into the mud. “Luo Hun, sir!”

“Struck dead by lightning…?” Luo Hun muttered, his eyes flashing like an animal’s as he walked up to Yang Qi. Reaching out with his hand, he sent a stream of energy into Yang Qi, only to find nothing unusual. His meridians and sea of energy were still destroyed, and his body was charred and blackened. “He was injured by the lightning strike, and his meridians and sea of energy are completely destroyed. But he’s alive.”

“Really?”

Even as Luo Hun inspected Yang Qi, a handful of men strode up, clad in luxuriously-tailored garments. They were important people from Yanhaven, one of which had long white hair, and seemed to be a steward from one of the clans in the city. After examining Yang Qi, he said, “Well, now we don’t have to bring this punk back for questioning. And we certainly don’t have to execute him. Send him back to the Yang Clan, and while you’re at it, send them this message from the city magistrate: because a Yang Clan delinquent stole a Latent Dragon Pill, the Yang Clan will provide full compensation, even if they have to sell every last belonging.”

“Yes sir!” The guards grabbed Yang Qi and began to drag him back to Yanhaven.

The night passed quickly, and soon, it was a bright, sunny day.

The violent storm the night before had destroyed a lot of crops and livestock, and the mighty Yan River outside of the city had flooded. But now, the rain was passed, and the temperature was already rising.

The Yang Clan, one of the most rich and powerful clans in Yanhaven, was completely abuzz. Servants scurried back and forth, the special guards were on high alert, and the servant girls, handmaidens, and older female servants were whispering amongst themselves in every corner of the clan.

A sharp-tongued old woman was currently in the middle of giving a vivid account of what had occurred, and although she tried to keep her voice down, it was impossible for her to hide her gloating smirk.

“Something major is going down for our Yang Clan, did you hear? Last night, Clan Lord Yang Zhan’s son Yang Qi stole a treasure from the city magistrate. He got beat up half to death, had his energy arts crippled, and was bound to a tree. Then he got struck by lightning! After they brought him back, he lay in bed all night, struggling to breathe. He could die at any moment….” [1]

Next to speak was one of the more faithful servants to the clan. “That’s right. And the city magistrate issued an ultimatum. The Yang Clan has three days to pay back the price of the stolen treasure, which means that the clan is going to go almost completely bankrupt….”

Many of the young servant girls were completely bowled over by that news. “The clan’s going to go bankrupt? How will we ever recover?”

“What about the other rich and powerful clans? Chen, Wang, Hong, and Li? They’ve never liked our Yang Clan, and will definitely jump at the chance to hit us while we’re down.”

“Yeah, the Yang Clan is in big trouble this time. That silkpants Yang Qi didn’t think at all about what he was doing, and ended up causing a huge disaster. Heh heh. His father Yang Zhan is the clan lord, but I bet his position isn’t going to be very stable after this.”

“Someone who works for the city magistrate told me that Yang Qi did it for a girl. That’s why he stole the treasure.”

“Bah! Silkpants like him are the most wicked scoundrels of all. They always cause problems!” One of the servants even went so far as to say, “It’s good thing his energy arts were crippled. Without any martial arts, he’ll be completely useless.”

Some of the servants were gloating in Yang Qi’s misfortune, others worried about the future of the clan, and some even cursed Yang Qi.

Meanwhile, in a courtyard in the middle of the clan, which was nested in a maze of corridors and verandas, a tall, well-built man in brocaded clothing stood listening to a report about the situation.

A doctor was currently speaking. “Lord, Young Master Yang Qi has been stabilized. But he suffered burns across almost his entire body. His meridians were destroyed and his sea of energy shattered. His martial arts were completely crippled! He’s going to be handicapped for the rest of his life!”

"Crippled his martial arts?” Yang Zhan said. “Destroyed his sea of energy…?”

BANG!

A massive palm strike smashed a nearby table into bits.

Splinters whistled through the air like wailing ghosts, many of them embedding into the ground nearby.

“The Yang Clan can compensate for a lost Latent Dragon Pill,” Yang Zhan continued, fuming. “But why did they have to cripple my son’s energy arts? Even cutting his arm off would have been better. With a limb lost, but his energy arts intact, he could still become a top expert. With crippled energy arts, he’ll never be able to converge energy.”

Also present was the clan steward. “Lord, what's done is done. There’s nothing we can do about it now. The critical matter at hand is that the city magistrate has demanded compensation for the Latent Dragon Pill. I'm afraid the chief elders won’t just stand by while the clan goes bankrupt. Someone is definitely going to take advantage of this situation to try to seize power….”

Yang Zhan snorted coldly. “Remember why I was able to seize the position of clan lord to begin with? It wasn’t by plotting, scheming and building alliances. It was because my energy arts and cultivation base were unmatchable. And that’s how things will remain. Let’s see if any of them are strong enough to take me out. Notify the chief elders that we’re going to have a clan forum in three days. We’ll talk things out with the subsidiary branches and figure out what to do. The city magistrate has given us enough time to raise the necessary money.”

“Yes, sir,” the steward said, nodding. He turned to leave, then stopped and asked, “What about Young Master Yang Qi? Considering the trouble he's caused, the chief elders definitely won't let him off the hook.”

“His martial arts were crippled and he was struck by lightning!” Yang Zhan said angrily. “Not even the city magistrate is interested in him. What are the chief elders going to do? Have him executed? If anybody dares to suggest laying a hand on my son, I won’t take the matter lying down. Another thing: I'm going to write a letter that I want delivered to Yang Qi’s aunt in the Demi-Immortal Institute.”

The steward's eyes brightened. “Right! How could I have forgotten that we have the Young Lady on our side?”

The Young Lady he referred to was Yang Zhan’s adoptive sister, and thus Yang Qi’s aunt. She was a member of the number one most domineering organization on the Rich-Lush Continent, the Demi-Immortal Institute, which gave her a very different identity than in the past. She had been away from the Yang Clan for ten years, and was spectacularly talented. After all, she had been tutored in cultivation by one of the elders of the Demi-Immortal Institute since she was very young.

“Divine Doctor Cao, how badly is Qi’er hurt?” Yang Zhan asked. “Is there any medicine that can wake him up? Your medical expertise is spoken of everywhere in Yanhaven. You must know of a way to treat his injuries.”

“I've applied a topical ointment,” the doctor replied, “and used my energy arts to perform a medical massage. He should be back on his feet in a few days. His organs weren’t damaged, just his meridians and sea of energy. Of course, he won't be able to practice cultivation after this.”

“Give ten energy convergence pills to Divine Doctor Cao as a reward,” Yang Zhan said, waving his hand. “When Qi’er wakes up, I’ll call for you again, doctor.”

Energy convergence pills were treated as currency in all of the shops and markets in the Rich-Lush Continent. They could also be used during the cultivation of energy arts to gather true energy, nourish the meridians, and expand the sea of energy.

“Yes sir….” the old steward said, leading the doctor away.

Yang Zhan remained behind. Clenching his hands into fists, he murmured, “Qi’er, your mother left so early. And now we're facing some major bad luck. I’ll do everything I can think of to restore your sea of energy, and make sure you can practice cultivation again. In the world we live in, it’s not an option to be so weak….”

In another location deep within the Yang Clan, Yang Qi was awake and laying there quietly in bed.

The room was adorned with red velvet furnishings and expensive, ancient paintings. There was even a copper incense burner decorated with turtles and cranes, burning a very expensive type of incense. The level of wealth on display was staggering.

It was hot outside, but a cool breeze drifted by the room, its source being the large, mist-covered pond there. Trees next to the pond provided shade, and there were also numerous blocks of ice which had been placed in the area to provide further cooling. Next to the door was a young servant girl about eleven or twelve years old, whose head continued to bob up and down as she fought the urge to sleep.

Yang Qi was no longer in pain. As he laid there, he attempted to ascertain what the lightning strike had done to him. When he closed his eyes, he could see what appeared to be a fist-sized mammoth made of lightning, resting in his sea of energy. Virtually any outside stimuli would cause the mammoth to suddenly shrink down until it was a tiny dot, which was a good thing, because any powerful experts who examined him would notice nothing unusual.

Yang Qi could sense that the lightning mammoth contained massive destructive power, power so great that, if he could somehow release it in an attack, it would probably destroy the entire mansion he was in.

He had been struck by lightning, but hadn’t died; instead, the electricity entered him and took the shape of a mammoth and an imp. No matter how Yang Qi considered the situation, he couldn’t come up with any explanation of what was going on.

At one point, Yang Qi circulated his energy, and the golden imp appeared in his forehead.

The imp then spoke into his mind, in a stentorian voice that no one else could hear.

“Fail to succeed, break to found. Unparalleled under heaven….”

1. Yang is a common surname that also means “poplar”. Zhan means “war, fight, battle”.